[Music]
Hello friends, I, Manoj Jaiswal,
heartily welcome you to this video. Today,
in this video, we're going to compare
two health insurance plans from ICICI Lombard.
Yes, on one side is Max
Protect and on the other side is Health Advantage.
We'll compare both plans to see
which plan is best for you and
which plan isn't.
You can also see which plan will be best for you
before buying the plan.
We'll understand the complete information within this plan:
what is the premium? What are the
basic details? What special features have been included? We're going to
see the complete information in this video. So, let's go to
our computer screen and understand the
comparison between these two plans. Now you're on my
computer screen, where we've
opened a presentation of ICICI Lombard's
Health Advantage. We're
going to compare it. Let's look at the complete review of ICICI Lombard's Max
Protect plan.
First, let's understand the unique features of the Health
Advantage S Plus plan.  The first
benefit is the Guaranteed [ __ ] Bonus, the second
is the Maternity Benefit Rider, which
is available in it for you. Thirdly, World
Wide Coverage is available in it, which has a co-payment of Rs.
10 per sum above Rs. 10 lakh and above that,
if we talk about Max Protect, then the
option of High Sum is available in it.
Second is World Wide Coverage without any co-
payment, like in A Advantage,
no co-payment is required in it.
Guaranteed [ __ ] Bonus will be available
in it, but it does not get reduced, meaning if there is
no claim, it will not get reduced. There
is unlimited refill for the same illness, there is
no restriction in it.
If we talk about the individual details,
see the name of the plan, as I told you, on the
left side you have ICC Health Advantage, on the
other side there is Max Protect, the
entry age in both is 18 years to 65
years, whereas if we talk about dependents, then the
maximum age kept is 25 years, the
policy term is one.  The maximum is one year, two years, three years. If we
talk about P Sub Insurance, then
under Health Advantage you get coverage of Rs 5 lakh to Rs 3 crore,
whereas under P Max Protect the
minimum is Rs 50 lakh and there is
no maximum limit. You can take as much as you want.
Home treatment is available
under ICC Loard which is Health Advantage
and the same
is available under P Max Protect but
above the premium variant. There are two variants like Premium Variant and
Classic Variant. It
is available under the premium variant. If we
talk about refill benefit, then the refill
benefit is available once in ASI Loard
for the same illness, be it any kind of illness,
whereas in ASI Loard which is Max product,
you get it for unlimited number of times. Its refill benefit is
world wide coverage of Rs
10 lakh available under ICC Loard for above Rs 10 lakh,
whereas it is available under P IC Max Protect
which
is premium mode.  Within that, there is a premium variant
and a maximum no
claim bonus of ₹ crore. If we talk about it, then the
minimum is 20% and the maximum is 100%.
Yes, and in both the cases, there will be
no reduction. If we
talk about day care procedures, then the award
is covered up to sum. Your domicile cover is also covered up to
sum ins. Shot organ donor
is also covered up to sum ins. If we talk about
AYUSH hospitalization, then that is also covered up to
sum ins. If we talk about emergency road ambulance, then
that is covered up to sum ins. If we
talk about room eligibility, then there is
no capping on room rent in Health Advantage. You can take any room. You
can take any room under Max Protect except Accept Suite. One thing has to be kept in
mind that the complete wellness
test which is maximum 000 under Health Advantage will be on
cashless basis.
You will not get it under Classic which is under Max product.  You get it
under the premium, you will get its chart
inside your brochure. Modern
treatment and robotic surgery which is covered
up to the sum included is under Max Protect,
if up to ₹ crore then one crore and the
premium plan is covered under it only.
You will have to take a rider for the non-payable item in it, but it will be included
under Max Protect.
Its premium is about
pre and post
hospitalization, so 60 days
and 180 days have been kept in both, pre will be 60 days and
post will be 180 days. E-consultation
is available for unlimited times. If you
talk about OPD cover, then OPD cover will have to be
added under it. It is not available under Health Advantage and
Max Pro.
If you want to take maternity cover, then
you can take it through a writer under Health Advantage.
This option is
not available under Max Pro. Waiting for PD, which is a
permanent exclusion, is included under it.  It is two
years and in Max Pro it is four years
but it can be reduced, there the
deductible is not available, no one is
available in it, the basic surgery is
covered up to 10 lakhs and in Max Pro the
covered up to sum is covered,
talking about the waiting period
in both the plans, the initial waiting period is
30 days, the specific exclusion has a
waiting period of two years, the
surgery has three years, if we
talk about the maternity waiting period, then there will be 9
months maternity coverage, there will be a
waiting period for maternity coverage, whereas it is
not available in Max Protect, but
yes, for maternity you will have to take a rider, if you
look inside the optional rider, then the first one
coming under Health Advantage is the
benefit rider, OPD claim protector,
sum protector is maternity benefit which
covers up to the delivery, personal
accident death, PTD and PPD, all
three options are available
inside Max Protect.  There is a
waiting period of two years for Assistant Deejay,
you can
downgrade or upgrade your plan,
due to this your premium can also be
affected a lot, so coming here the
presentation is complete, so this
was the complete information in which we
understood IIC Lombard's Max product
and Health Advantage, which of these two
plans did you like the best and which
special feature did you like, please do comment in the comment box,
otherwise if you have any
feedback please do use the comment box,
if you liked the video then
like the video and share it with maximum people,
otherwise if you have not yet subscribed to the channel then
please do
not forget to subscribe to the channel, in the end thank
you very much for watching this video completely
[Music]